Subtitle edited By iMR aka imxpress
Asakusa, last stop, Asakusa.
We don't have much time. Go to work. Saya?
Something wrong?
Every bloodsucker you kill brings us
one step closer.
- I'm not here for those bottom feeders.
- It's only a matter of time and patience.
Jesus Christ!
- Hey! Something's not right.
- What?
That ain't no bloodsucker in there.
He's human.
It didn't have time to transform,
that's all.
You're gonna take her word for it?
What if she just screwed up?
Saya, that's enough.
Get some rest. I'll be at the hotel tomorrow.
- The little bitch is out of control.
- We need her.
Saya is all we've got.
Michael, we're done here.
Michael?
Let's go.
Saya sama!
Kato. Tell me about my father.
He was a warrior.
The bravest hunter there was.
How did he tell demons apart from humans?
He stared straight into their eyes,
and he could see they had no souls.
Demons can assume human flesh,
but they can't conjure up human soul.
Heaven put demons into the world
to test our virtues.
If Heaven intended for demons
to live among us,
why do we kill them?
In life we all have duties.
To fulfill our duties is serving Heaven's will.
The rest is not for us to question.
Saya!
Your father was slain
by Onigen,
the oldest, vilest demon of them all.
It's your destiny
to avenge him,
to continue his mission.
Are you determined, my girl?
Yes, Kato.
Three deaths on the American air base
within a week.
Our cleaners got there in time.
No one saw the bodies.
- The underlings are feeding.
- Well, you know the old saying,
"When the hungry demons feed
without discretion...
"...Onigen is near."
You're about to get your wish.
To face the leader of the pack.
- The plan?
- The Council wants you on the base
- to find more leads.
- I don't investigate. I kill.
Be my guest.
Kill the bottom feeders and lure out Onigen.
- But this time, let the blood mutate.
- I was never wrong.
Doesn't hurt to be cautious, that's all.
And don't blow your cover
unless absolutely necessary.
The Elder pulled a lot of strings
to arrange this.
Cover?
- What's that?
- It's a new outfit.
You know, Dad, you don't have to drive
me to school every day. I can walk.
Don't be silly. It's my only chance
to spend some time with you.
- Everyone else walks.
- You're not everyone, sweetie.
- I'm not a kid, either.
- Is that why you did it?
- To prove that you're all grown up?
- Did what?
I was hoping you'd come clean.
That's what grown-ups do, you know.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Well, I...
I guess it must've been Frank.
What do you say, Frank?
- Sir?
- Was it you who took my car out
- for a spin last night?
- No, sir.
Did you sneak off the base and boogie
at the Hippy Shake until 4:00?
- No, sir.
- I cannot believe this. You're spying on me?
I don't have to, Alice. You're my daughter.
People know you and people talk.
Okay, yeah, I'm sorry.
I should have told you. Just...
You're always busy, day and night,
working on your second star.
You've gotta understand, we're at war.
We're all at risk, even here.
- This is your war, not mine.
- That's enough, Alice.
- Hey! Watch where you're going, damn it!
- Yes, sir!
- Momma, Momma, can't you see?
Alice! Alice, would you come back here?
The Air Force made a man of me
Alice!
I'm so happy, I'm so proud
So, class, let's give our new classmate
a warm welcome.
There we go. Saya, would you care
to take that desk over there?
Good! Now, I know
you've all been doing your homework,
and you've prepared today's readings,
which will be
from Mary Shelley's Frankenstein.
- Okey-dokey, we're gonna start on page 135.
- Hey.
- She must be lost? Thinks it's a navy base.
- I can't believe they let a Jap enroll here.
Next thing you know,
they think they own the place.
"Like Adam, I was..."
Yes, sir. Our story stands.
They think it's a CIA plan.
Frankenstein's monster compares himself
with both Adam and Lucifer.
Can you tell me why, Liz?
Because both Adam and Lucifer
were created by God?
Yes, but these are opposite ends
of good and evil.
To which end does the monster belong?
To whom does he reach out in his anger?
Saya, would you care
to join our discussion?
Me no English.
Yes, Alice?
Anger is what makes the monster human.
It's neither good nor evil.
He was abandoned
by his creator just like Lucifer.
So God and Victor Frankenstein
both deserted their creations
not because they were imperfect,
but because they reminded them
of their own imperfections.
That's very interesting.
So, do you think that God
- is an irresponsible father figure?
- She must be thinking about her dad.
- What did you say?
- Piss off the princess
and next thing you know,
her dad will court-martial you.
It's not my fault.
Please, don't send me to the chair.
- Yes, now can we...
- Grow up!
...settle down, please.
Come on, let's be nice.
George, could you read the next paragraph?
"Accursed creator!
Why did you form a monster so hideous
"that even you turned from me in disgust?
God, in pity, made man..."
Concentrate, Alice.
Let the mind lead the body.
Good!
That's it for today.
What's our motto, Team Lupin?
- Be a wolf or be gone!
- That's the spirit!
I need your help with this.
- For the team, understand?
- I think so.
- Alice!
- Sir?
You're dragging down the whole team.
- I want you to stay and practice.
- But I have to...
Don't think
you're gonna get special treatment
- just 'cause you're the General's daughter.
- I didn't say that.
- I'll spar with Alice.
- And I will be the ref.
- No, I'll practice on my own.
- Gotta think of the team.
Think of the tournament next week.
- Make a wolf of Alice for me, girls.
- Yes, Mr. Powell.
Bring it on.
- What are you doing?
- We tried very, very hard to ignore you.
But you just keep getting on our nerves!
Are you insane?
Go.
Secure that vehicle!
- Who are they?
- We don't know yet, sir.
Step out!
Unlock the doors and step out right now.
- Hey, pal. What do you think you're doing?
- Stop right there, fellow.
Easy, big guy. Do we look like Vietcong?
You keep your hands
where I can see them, wiseass!
- Is that necessary?
- General.
Michael Harrison,
Director of Operations, CIA.
- Those men work for us.
- What are you spooks doing on my base?
- That's classified.
- Langley sent us to assist
- with the war effort.
- In what capacity?
Last time I checked,
D.O. Doesn't come under your jurisdiction.
- Am I talking to you?
- General, my superior will call you shortly.
Now I suggest we all calm down
and handle this
like the professionals we are.
- Shall we?
- You keep an eye on them, Frank.
Yes, sir.
They were here. I saw them.
Sharon... Linda's head was...
It's okay, sweetie, you're safe now.
That's all that matters.
I saw them!
The Japanese girl, Frank.
Why was she in our school?
- Washington arranged her enrollment, sir.
- Washington?
Well, registrar says her name is Saya.
She's the daughter of Motoki Shishikura,
a soon-to-be-appointed ambassador to D.C.
Well, you confirm that with our local liaison.
You get a warrant issued and find her.
They cleaned it all up!
Dad, look, it's still wet.
We gotta find out
what these guys are doing, Frank.
That could be a problem, sir. We don't have
the authority to detain Agency personnel.
I'll deal with that.
I respectfully disagree, sir.
Then I will have to file an official
complaint with the Pentagon.
I understand, sir.
Dad, whoever they are, they've covered
up two murders. You can't let them go.
- Cut them loose, Frank. Alice.
- Yes, sir. Stand down!
You son of a bitch.
What's wrong with you,
taunting Mckee like that?
In case you didn't notice,
they pulled their guns on me.
We've gotta clean up this mess
or the Council will have our heads.
What's the Elder thinking, anyway,
sending Saya into a high school?
- She's older than all of us combined!
- Yeah.
Christ.
The Elder wants to see us.
Something was wrong with them!
Linda's blood...
Sweetie, you're still in shock.
It's understandable. You go get some sleep.
You have to believe me.
Mr. Powell knows something!
How can he know anything
if he wasn't even there?
- Now would you just go get some sleep!
- Dad, you're wrong.
Alice, that's enough! Look,
would you just leave it to the grown-ups?
We'll talk in the morning.
Yes? Frank, what do you have?
Yeah, just as I said.
If there were to be a new ambassador,
I would have been briefed.
Guys with sunglasses and funny hats
wave their cheap badges around
and I'm supposed to believe
they're sent by Langley?
Do what ever you have to.
Find out who they are
and what the hell they're doing on my base!
Sir.
Sit.
- Everything according to plan?
- Yes, sir.
Rumor has it Mckee
was calling Langley and Washington.
Very curious about both of you.
Was that part of your plan?
We had a run-in with him, yes.
Having American friends in high places
doesn't mean I'm Uncle Sam.
A little discretion would be nice.
The Council has to remain anonymous.
Our American connections
cannot risk exposure.
Don't get too cozy playing CIA.
I'll take care of it. Leave it to me.
You have my word, sir.
- Hungry?
- Starving.
Here's something to curb your appetite.
A plane crashed in the Okutama Mountains
this morning.
Those are the crew members onboard,
what's left of them, anyway.
This is Onigen's work.
Those photos were taken
before we cleaned up the scene.
No one else knows.
- She's here? She took the bait.
- Yes.
Now, Onigen's here, blood will be shed.
I'm sorry, sir, ma'am.
The Onsen opens 24 hours.
Feel free to enjoy anytime.
Anything else you need?
I see you have no luggage.
Observant and caring.
Your wife is a lucky lady.
Yes. If only she thinks so.
She and my daughters are preparing dinner.
It will be ready soon in the dining hall.
I can't believe that!
I'm sorry.
Come out and play, my children.
The feeding season has begun.
Mr. Powell, how are you?
- How's life?
- Six pence half a shilling.
- You can do the conversion to yen.
- The usual?
On the rocks.
Hi, dear Alice, welcome!
So, what's your poison tonight?
Leave us, Hide.
You lied.
You knew Linda and Sharon were gonna
hurt me and you lied to my dad.
Why me? What did I do?
What... What do you want from me?
It's all about you, you, you, isn't it?
What if you're wrong? Delusional?
- You ever thought about that?
- I know what I saw.
What you see has got nothing to do
with what's real.
You look around, you see an air base
run by Daddy, flying his B-52s
to wipe out gook farmers in rice paddies,
fighting his righteous war.
But you don't see the real war,
the one that's been going on
since the beginning of time
between your kind and mine.
And the end is upon you, brought on
by your self-deceiving Godliness
and your pretentious moral high ground.
We will come out the victors.
Welcome to the other side
of the looking glass.
Now it's time to die.
Hey! Hey, stop! Stop! Hey, please!
No, no!
Let her go!
No!
Get down.
He's getting away.
He's wounded. Get closer!
Faster!
Get closer!
Closer!
- I'm a demon?
- No!
You have a human soul!
What is it? She's near?
Mr. Powell, Sharon and Linda,
- all of them...
- They never existed.
What exactly were they?
Bloodsuckers.
They take on human form.
It's the way they live.
So I guess you're not
really a student, are you?
- Are there more of those things out there?
- More than you can imagine.
- Anything I can do?
- It's not your war. Go home.
- And forget everything.
- And leave you fighting them alone?
I can take care of myself.
My dad is the general at the base.
I could tell him, and...
- Don't tell anyone!
- Why?
You want to live?
You want your father to live?
Then don't!
All right. He wouldn't believe me, anyway.
Saya.
Be really careful, okay?
- Did they see you?
- No, sir.
- Are these weapons?
- No, I don't think so.
There were a total of four cases.
All seemed like standard issues,
as far as I can tell, sir.
From the Agency?
Well, that's if these guys
are actually from the Agency at all.
Call up the tech guys.
What in God's name are these things?
Slugs, snails and puppy dog's tails.
Easy.
I'm here to talk, that's all.
- How dare you enter my home uninvited?
- My apologies.
Old habits die hard.
I've been with the Agency
one day too long I guess.
What do you want?
Did you authorize the burglary, General?
You're not taking it back. It's evidence.
- Of what?
- That's for Central Command to decide.
Wait! General.
I know we started off on the wrong foot.
It's my fault.
But we’re on the same side, I assure you.
The side that murdered
two high school girls? I don't think so.
I have come here to give you Saya, General.
She's not with the Agency.
I can't be held responsible.
She's out of control.
Where is she? Get this down, Frank.
Hotel Yuzuya. Togoshi-ginza Street.
Ni-Cho, five seven...
Hang on. Tell me the street again?
Togoshi-ginza.
I know it. It's in the Shinagawa ward.
About 30 minutes from here...
You left me no choice, General.
I couldn't leave the case with you.
Who are you people?
Saviors of the human race.
The Council has been around
since before your granddaddy's granddaddy
stole his land from the Indians.
We walk a higher path, General.
Run, Alice, run!
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Dad. Dad?
Alice, get off the base!
- Alice, you're not safe here.
- I don't know what to do.
Alice, leave, leave.
I love you, sweetie.
Dad. Dad! Dad!
Fucking A!
They were taken at the Onsen Hotel.
Onigen.
She's looking for you.
It's time we fought back.
Everything is being arranged.
But it's not gonna be easy.
I don't care!
The Council finds Onigen for me,
that's the deal.
It's already taken too long.
You ever think about the future,
after this?
There is more to life than Onigen.
Not for me.
Damn!
How did you find me?
They killed him.
You were right. She showed.
Copy that. I'm on my way. Take her out.
Take her out now! Do it now!
Do it! Now! Hurry up!
The people you work for, they killed my dad!
- I don’t work for them.
- You're lying!
Thank you.
I kill the bloodsuckers.
They provide me what I need to survive.
That's all.
Why my dad? Why?
I'll find out from...
Down!
- Give me the girl, Saya!
- No.
This has nothing to do with you.
Don't mess with me, halfling!
Luke?
- Michael.
- Put down the gun.
- Put it down.
- He killed Mckee.
Are you insane?
What the hell do you think you're doing?
My job! I've cleaned up the mess, haven't I?
You're making a bigger mess!
Not when I get that girl.
- No.
- Luke,
I'm not gonna tell you again.
You're not really gonna shoot me, Michael.
Try me.
Okay, you win.
But don't think I'm not gonna
tell the Elder all about this.
Be my guest. 'Cause I'm not the one
jeopardizing our mission.
- You're getting soft, old man.
- Maybe. But not stupid!
You all right?
Who's stupid now?
We have to go.
Wait.
You drive.
Radio Free Japan. Top of the hour.
The commanding officer of right
Air Force base, General Howard R. Mckee,
has died of a heart attack.
The General was discovered in critical
condition at his home a few hours ago.
The doctors on the scene
were unable to resuscitate him.
Authorities are asking your help
in finding his daughter, Alice Mckee,
who fled the base in an Air Force truck
shortly after hearing the news.
A base psychiatrist
describes the teen as unstable
and cautions that her life may be at risk.
Saya?
Saya, are you okay? Saya?
Wake up.
Saya, wake up.
Your blood.
Why did you save me?
I'm not your kind.
It was the right thing to do.
The right thing...
I used to know right from wrong.
Life used to feel right.
Kato raised me in the mountain village,
where I called home,
where I found the only friend in my life.
Happiness and love was within reach.
But then, the dark dream came.
In the dream, I killed him. Love was gone,
replaced by blood.
Saya! Saya sama!
Then I woke up, and it was not a dream.
What's happened?
Come, my girl. We have to go.
Take your father's sword!
I don't understand.
This sword has gathered dark powers
from all the demons it has slain.
It's a blessing
and a curse.
One you're not yet ready for.
But we have no time.
Demons have found us.
Kato...
Don't come out till I tell you to!
Don't follow me!
We go together!
No!
Kato.
It's time to be on your own, my girl.
What are you going to do?
My duty.
No, Kato!
Stay out of sight
until you're truly ready
to face the demons.
Now go and don't look back.
You okay?
You're thinking about your father?
Just...
Just all the little things.
What about you?
You have family?
My mother,
I never knew her.
My father,
he died days after I was born.
How?
Onigen murdered him.
The oldest, most powerful demon.
My father's most loyal retainer,
Kato, saved me.
He took me into the mountains,
cared for me, trained me to be strong,
to be like my father.
In the end, he died for me.
Kato!
Many a night,
Kato told me about my father's murder,
how demons deceived him
in the most despicable way.
That day I finally understood.
I'm my father's daughter,
but I'm also the evil that killed him.
Since that night,
time stopped.
I live for one purpose and one purpose only,
to kill Onigen.
That's my duty.
Kato was right.
Demons can't conjure up human souls.
Promise me one thing, also.
Never doubt yourself.
You're human.
I promise.
So much pain. So much struggle. Silly girl.
She's close by. Bring her to me.
Alive?
Still holding a grudge?
The halfling owes me.
Don't be ridiculous.
Her power is far beyond what it used to be.
We will see about that!
Let me out.
What?
You go alone.
Too dangerous to stay with me.
No. It's our war now.
Come on!
Start!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah! Yeah, yeah.
Alice!
- Dad, don't go.
- It's me! It's me, Alice!
Please wake up!
Okay, let's go!
Saya!
Alice. Alice.
This isn't really happening.
Any of it.
You.
You're alive.
Saya!
He isn't real!
This isn't really happening. None of it!
No. He's alive.
No. No.
You finally found me.
And I found you.
Look at you, my girl.
Eaten alive by guilt over a single human,
yet not a glimmer of regret for having
slaughtered so many of your own kind.
I'm not your kind.
Denial. Stubbornness.
You are, after all, your father's child.
I see you've taken good care of his sword.
- Show me your true form, Onigen!
- What do you want to see?
The demon who murdered my father.
The demon who I'll kill.
You knew all along, didn't you,
deep down in your heart?
I gave you your strength.
I gave you your power.
I gave you immortality,
my daughter.
No!
Silly girl, you've suffered long enough.
Come to me.
I've waited a long time, Saya,
for you to gain your strength, to be ready.
You think the more demons you kill,
the more human you become, don't you?
How naive.
The truth is, the more you kill,
the more you unleash your power.
You've come to your true nature.
Don't you see?
You've been doing everything you could
to become what you don’t want to be.
- To become me.
- Never!
It's your destiny, silly girl.
Leaves fall, forest grows on.
The future lies in you.
Let her go!
Alice! Alice!
Alice!
Don't you see now?
Which half of you gives you strength,
which half makes you feeble?
Let it all go. Unleash yourself.
You gave birth to me, and you can kill me,
but you're nothing to me!
You don't know
what it means to be a mother!
Kill me, my daughter. Kill me.
And become me!
Saya?
Saya.
Are you okay?
What's the point? You don't believe me.
These monsters,
you said one of them attacked
the army truck you stole.
But, when we found you
at the bottom of the ravine, you were alone.
They cleaned it up.
- They?
- The Council.
They killed my father.
Yes.
General Mckee,
mortally wounded by the sidearm
of Sergeant Frank Nielsen.
Sergeant Nielsen lost his son
in the war three months ago.
His psych evaluations show instability.
And this girl you mentioned, Saya, I believe.
Her name, her identity were false.
In fact, we believe she's not even Japanese.
Where is she right now?
She's out there.
Searching.
Searching for what?
Searching for a way back
from the other side of the looking glass.